2048年
The year is 2048.
技術發展不再循規蹈矩
Evolving technologies can no longer be regulated.
YYeTs人人影視
■
本字幕由
人人影視字幕組
翻譯
禁止用作任何
商業盈利行為
危險的技術進步讓犯罪形態從此改變
Dangerous advancements forever alter the criminal landscape.
■
面條打包子
Reginamoon
michael
feilixiaozi
衛老哥
阿包包
胖兔純
七七
CS小明漫畫家
Al_ice
冬麟
Silence
■
翻譯
警察未做好準備
Police are not prepared.
執法機關建立新的防線
Law enforcement combats this corruption
與罪惡進行斗爭
with a new line of defense...
■
圈圈
青椒
早先森
校對
但他們生來并不平等
But not all are created equal.
■
阿阿阿包
憑陵新月
雪貴人
■
時間軸
DRN系列的設計理念是希望盡可能像人類一樣
The idea behind the DRNs was to be as human as possible.
他們基于一個叫合成靈魂的開發程序
They were based on a program called synthetic soul.
■
MythCreator  吉吉
特效
是那批瘋狂機器人吧
That's one of the crazy ones.
-我打頭陣  -行動
- I'll lead you in? - Let's go.
■
壓制
如今所有警察  包括人類和機器人
Now all cops-- human and manmade together--
共同投入戰斗  保衛我們
take on the battle to watch over us all.
總監
紫玉
機器之心
第一季  第十二集
♬They sleep♬
♬And sleepwalk♬
♬They dissolve to dreams♬
♬Hear children crying♬
♬They're losing everything♬
歡迎來到第十七洞
Welcome to the 17th hole.
布萊恩·巴羅準備開球
Brian Barrow on the tee.
球徑直飛向了...
And straight up the middle...
♬For all we know♬
♬There's nothing changed♬
媒體關閉
Media off.
你不接電話嗎
Are you going to answer that?
不接
No.
薩曼莎來電
是薩曼莎的電話
It's Samantha.
沒錯
Yep.
別接  多里安
Hey, no, Dorian...
我替約翰·肯尼思接的
Uh, John Kennex's line.
他現在不想跟你說話
Uh, he does not wish to speak with you right now.
他正在揮手做手勢
He is waving his hands,
意思是"不要"
gesturing "No."
是的  我明白
Yes, I understand.
我也很煩他那么做
I hate it when he does that, too.
對  我知道
Yeah, I know.
他的毛病還多著呢
That's the least of his problems.
好的
Okay.
你保重
You take care.
你需要我轉達她的留言嗎
Would you like me to relay her message?
不用  我猜得到
No, I think I got it.
謝了
Thanks.
你想跟我談談嗎
Do you want to talk about it?
昨晚薩曼莎和我一起吃了晚飯
Samantha and I had dinner last night...
作伴的還有她室友  她媽媽
and the hologram of her roommate
和她的理療師的全息影像
and her mom and her therapist.
每一通打來的電話她都要接
Every single call she got, she took.
她把你全息屏蔽掉了
She holo-blocked you.
沒錯  兩個人就不能
Exactly. I mean, whatever happened to two people
好好地吃頓飯聊聊天嗎  你明白嗎
just sharing a meal and connecting, you know?
-我明白  -你才不明白
- I know. - You wouldn't know.
為什么我要問你  你知道就怪了
Why am I asking you? You wouldn't have a clue.
好吧  我只是假設
Well-- and I'm just positing this--
說不定是因為你太悶了
perhaps you're boring.
我悶  你說我悶
Boring? You're calling me boring?
我們得談談男人間的相處之道了
We need to talk about guy code.
這種事不應該...
There's certain things you don't do...
我需要你們幫我查一宗疑似謀殺案
Hey, I need you to help me check out a possible homicide.
沒問題  什么時候報的警
Sure. When did the call come in?
沒人報警
It didn't.
也沒有強行進入的痕跡  沒有打斗
There's no sign of forced entry, no struggle.
看起來完全沒有犯罪痕跡
No foul play indicated at all.
急救人員認為是心臟驟停
EMTs are calling it cardiac arrest.
我不明白
I don't understand.
為什么你認為這可能是謀殺案
Why is it considered a possible homicide?
受害人是個改造人
The victim's a chrome.
我們的基因被改造過了
We're genetically engineered.
我們不會英年早逝
We don't die young.
死者名叫布萊恩·巴羅  28歲
The deceased's name is Brian Barrow, 28.
凱恩資產管理公司的證券交易員
Bond trader at Kane Asset Management.
怪不得家里是這樣的  丟什么東西了嗎
Explains the view. Anything missing?
據報告看  沒有
According to the report, no.
排除搶劫這一可能動機  他的病歷呢
Rules out robbery as a likely motive. Medical history?
他是典型的改造人
Typical chrome.
沒有健康問題
No health issues.
世界級的運動員  是個游泳健將
World-class athlete, a swimmer.
他參加了2036年的底特律奧運會
He competed in the Detroit Olympics of 2036.
他暴病而死在邏輯上是說不通的
There's no logical explanation for this.
他怎么可能以這種方式死去
How could he die like this?
我們應該做個毒物學測試
We should do a toxicology.
說不定急救人員說的沒錯呢
Maybe EMTs got it right:
他是心臟病突發
heart attack.
不可能  當一個改造人被設計出來時
No. When a chrome is designed,
他的每一部分都被仔細檢查過了
every box is checked:
健康情況  外貌  智商
health, beauty, intelligence.
我知道改造人不應該有什么先天性缺陷
Look, I know chromes aren't supposed to have congenital defects;
他們的一切都是完美的
perfect genes and all that.
但是改造人一般也不會來當警察啊
Chromes don't normally become cops, either.
萬事總有第一次
There's a first time for everything.
瞧瞧這個
Look at this.
這兒有個半毫米的穿刺傷口
There's a half-millimeter puncture wound
在他的顱腔底部
at the base of his skull.
直接穿到了他的大腦皮層
It goes all the way to his cerebral cortex.
你能提取一些DNA嗎
Can you get any DNA?
有什么問題嗎
Something wrong?
假如兇手是通過這個傷口將其謀殺的話
If this is the entry point to something that killed him,
那DNA顯示
the DNA indicates
布萊恩·巴羅是被七個不同的人殺死的
that Brian Barrow was murdered by seven different people.
亞力克·戈文  菲利普·摩西  七個人了
...Alec Govain, Philip Moses makes seven.
我們在兇案受害人的傷口里
And these are the seven people whose DNA we found
是找到了這七個人的DNA嗎
in the wound of the murder victim?
沒錯
Correct.
不管殺害布萊恩·巴羅的武器是什么
Whatever weapon was used to kill Brian Barrow
它都被所有這些人的DNA污染了
was contaminated by the DNA of all these people.
你找到他們在哪里了嗎
Did you locate them?
他們都已經死了
They're all dead.
他們都被注明是自然死亡
They're all listed as dying of natural causes.
他們的心臟停跳了
Their hearts stopped.
你覺得這到底是怎么回事  約翰
What do you think's going on, John?
我不知道
I don't know,
但我懷疑他們并不是自然死亡
but I doubt they died of natural causes.
這些人是改造人嗎
Are these people chromes?
他們不是  但他們被選中一定是有原因的
They are not, but they must have been chosen for a reason.
你覺得我們是無意間發現了一個連環殺手嗎
Do you think we stumbled upon a serial killer?
是的  要不是他殺了那個改造人
Yeah. If he hadn't killed the chrome,
我們永遠都不會發現他
we never would have picked this up.
脖子后面的一個小針孔
It would be pretty easy to miss
是很容易被忽視掉的
a little pinprick on the back of the neck.
他們有什么共同點
What do they have in common?
他們都住在市內
They all lived in city limits.
除此之外  我們的算法還沒發現其他的共同點
Other than that, our algorithms didn't pick up any patterns.
我倒是發現了一個共同點
I see one pattern.
他們都很有吸引力
They're all very attractive.
再來一次
Do it again.
我們得停手了
We have to stop.
你照我說的做  不然我就報警
You will do what I want, or I will call the police,
那樣你下半輩子就只能待在監獄里了
and you will go to jail for the rest of your life
你這可是被吊銷營業執照后非法營業
for practicing with a revoked license.
你自己選吧
Your choice.
有人向媒體泄露了改造人謀殺案
Someone's been talking to the press about the chrome murder.
你開玩笑吧  已經泄露了
You're kidding. Already?
"警方在追捕一名疑似專門獵殺
"Metro Police hunt for possible serial killer
市里年輕俊男美女的連環殺手"
targeting the city's young and beautiful."
洛杉磯時報  紐約時報  美聯社死亡專線
L.A. Times, New York Times, AP Deathwire.
我的通訊設備一直響個不停
My comm's been ringing off the hook.
我們都還什么都不了解
We don't even know anything yet,
他們就已經開始報道了
and they're already talking about it.
這種新聞很受關注
This kind of news sells.
改造人在全城都有耳目
Chromes have ears all over the city,
他們很關心自己的同類
and they take care of their own.
我有條線索
Now, I have a lead.
在死者被害前兩個小時
Two hours before the victim was killed,
他去過雷明頓的伊萊克特斯俱樂部
he was at the Electus Club on Remington.
兇手可能是從俱樂部開始跟蹤他的
Killer could have followed him from the club.
我去查一下
I'll check it out.
其實  應該我去
Actually, I should go.
我一個人去
Alone.
伊萊克特斯是個改造人俱樂部
The Electus is a chrome club.
好吧  你去合適
Of course. Makes sense.
我們去魯迪那邊看看
We'll go check in with Rudy.
其他死者的遺體正送去他那里
The bodies of the other victims are on the way to him.
如果他們的脖子上都有相同的傷口
If they have the same wounds on the back of their neck,
我們或許就能知道是什么害死了他們
maybe he can find out what killed them.
你確定要去改造人的俱樂部嗎
You sure you're up for going to the chrome club?
是的  他們可能并不尊重我的人生選擇
Yeah. They may not respect what I've done with my life,
但他們應該尊重我為他們做的事
but they sure respect what I can do for theirs.
布萊恩·巴羅死后他們第一個打電話給了你
You were the first one they called when Brian Barrow died.
這只是因為他們希望那是謀殺
Only because they're praying it was murder.
如果布萊恩·巴羅是自然死亡
If Brian Barrow died of natural causes,
這些改造人就要面臨一個
the chromes would have to face something
他們認為不可能的情況
they never thought possible.
改造人最大的賣點就是壽命長久
The whole selling point of being a chrome is a long life.
還有十分健康
And perfect health.
他們為此可是花了很多錢的
People pay a lot of money for perfection.
你有什么需要隨時告訴我
Let me know if you need anything.
羅伯特  維奧萊特  歡迎
Robert, Violet, welcome.
很高興見到你們
Nice to see you.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
這是私人俱樂部
This is a private club.
我也很抱歉  不過我是會員
I'm sorry, too, that I'm a member.
瓦萊麗·斯塔警探
Detective Valerie Stahl.
我要看一下你們昨天的監控錄像
I need to see your surveillance data from yesterday.
你是一名警察
You're a police officer?
你可是改造人啊
You're a chrome.
是的  我已經給你看過我的警徽了
Yeah, I just showed you my badge,
我知道你視力正常不近視
and I know you have 20/20 vision.
其實我視力比一般人要好  但我恐怕幫不了你
20/10. And I'm afraid I can't help you.
我正在調查一名叫
I'm investigating the murder
布萊恩·巴羅的改造人的謀殺案
of a chrome named Brian Barrow.
我相信你在新聞里也看到了
I'm sure you heard about it on the news.
作為總經理  我有責任保護
As general manager, I'm responsible for protecting
我們所有會員的隱私
the privacy of our members.
可能我說得不清楚
Maybe I'm not making myself clear.
我們認為兇手是從這里跟蹤他回家的
We believe his killer may have followed him from here.
這樣的話  他應該出現在
In that case, he would show up
警察的無人機視線里  對吧
on the police drones, wouldn't he?
再說一遍  這是私人
Again, this is a private...
俱樂部  是的  我知道  我想你也知道
Club. Yes, I know, and I'm sure you're smart enough to know
我只要45秒就能拿到搜查令
that I can get a search warrant in about 45 seconds.
那你也應該知道
And you must be smart enough to know
我能讓索恩首席法官
that I can get Chief Judge Thorne
10秒鐘之后就把它撤銷
to quash it ten seconds after that.
-他也是會員  -那我就迫不得已
- He's a member. - I guess I'll just be forced
要減少你們一半的巡邏警力了
to cut your police patrol by 50%.
-你是想嚇唬我嗎  -是的
- Is that supposed to scare me? - Should.
根據統計模型  這會使
Based on statistical models, it'll trigger
這個區域的暴力案件上升32%
a 32% rise in violent attacks in the area.
罪犯們發現巡邏警察不像以前那么多了
Criminals find out we're not patrolling like we used to,
他們就會利用這個機會
and they're gonna take advantage.
很快這里就會成為案件多發區域
Before you know it, this is a high-incident area.
這個道理你懂的
You know how that works.
我們不需要警察
We don't need the police.
我們有私人保安
We have private security.
你是說走廊里的那個人
You mean the guy in the hallway
違反了《武器管制法》第49條第二款嗎
violating the concealed weapons statute 49B?
這個即使是索恩法官也不好辦吧
That's a lot to sweep under the rug, even for Judge Thorne.
-打擾了  有什么問題嗎  -有啊
- Sorry. Is there a problem? - Yeah.
你們就沒有個更難對付的人嗎
Do you have anyone a little more formidable?
別看我
Oh, not me.
我一碰就傷
I bruise easily.
改造人可沒那么容易受傷
Chromes don't bruise easily.
你真是個不錯的警官  我是這里的所有人
Ah, you are a good police officer. I'm the owner.
想進來坐坐嗎
You want to sit?
當然
I'd love to.
我叫杰克·貝爾曼
Jake Bellman.
你覺得是改造人
Do you think it was a chrome
把我們的調查泄露給了媒體嗎
that leaked our investigation to the press?
有這個可能
It's possible.
他們的影響力可不小
They got a lot of pull in this town.
你知道每年這里會發生
Do you know how many murders there are
多少起謀殺案嗎
in this city every year?
-756起  -那可不是小數目
- 756. - Yeah, a lot.
結果有個被害人是改造人  突然之間
One of them turns out to be a chrome, and suddenly
世界都停轉了
the whole world stops.
恰好證明了我的觀點
Just proves my point.
什么觀點
What point?
案子里的那種技術
That technology, in this case
改造人不斷地挑撥大眾
chromes, is driving a wedge between people.
將改造人和普通人對立起來
Making it us versus them.
科技  就好比跟人約會被晾在一邊
Technology, like being holo-blocked on a date.
都是因為你這個人很悶
I thought we agreed that you had a bad date
所以約會才失敗的對吧
because you're boring.
你就是沒法接受
You just can't handle the fact
科技也是問題的一部分這一事實
that technology's part of the problem.
進步太快讓你難以適應
Cuts a little close to the titanium.
才不是  我也很喜歡這種反科技的
No, in fact, I'm excited to embrace this new,
-嶄新的生活方式  -真的嗎
- anti-tech lifestyle. - Really?
回警局的時候
On the way back to the precinct,
我們把你的機械腿換成木頭腿吧
let's replace your robotic leg with a tree limb.
或是換個實用的鐵鍬什么的
Or maybe something useful, like a shovel.
換成鐵鍬就好了
I wish I had a shovel.
我十八歲的時候是個律師
I was an attorney at 18,
所以我知道警探
so I know that detectives
無權削減巡邏人數
can't cut police patrols.
我總會找到方法拿到那份錄像的
I'm gonna get that footage one way or the other.
一個改造人被殺了
A chrome was killed.
是你俱樂部的一員
A member of your club.
也是你的同類
One of your own.
我們想知道前因后果
We want to know what the story is.
我也想知道你的往事
Okay, well, I want to know what your story is.
為什么  就因為我是個警察
Why, 'cause I'm a police officer?
讓你好奇了嗎
I'm a curiosity to you?
不是因為那個  但我的確好奇
No, but I am curious.
我的故事說來話長了
It's a long story.
我有時間
Well, I've got time.
是嗎  你不用回去嗎
Yeah? You don't need to get back to your club?
不用
No.
當警察并不是改造人所選的
Being a cop, it's not the strangest
最匪夷所思的生活方式
life choice I've heard for a chrome.
我哥哥是個雕塑家
You know, my brother's a sculptor.
想知道他的雕塑手法是什么嗎
You want to know what his medium is?
當然
Sure.
你聽說過鏈鋸嗎
You ever heard of a chain saw?
-聽過  -鏈鋸和廢木頭
- Yes. - Chain saw and lumber.
就是他的工具和原料
That's his medium.
沒幾個畫廊喜歡那種東西
Not too many galleries for something like that.
我覺得他們把他的創造力基因改造過頭了
I think they kind of overdid his creative gene.
我相信你想象得出改造后的孩子
I can imagine you'd know how my parents felt
與期望不同時我父母的感受
having a chrome who didn't meet their expectations.
你同情他嗎
You pity him?
不  他同情我們
No. He pities us.
他很驕傲地自稱雕刻家
He's proud to call himself a sculptor.
他很快樂
He's happy.
那你呢
What about you?
你會驕傲地自稱警察嗎
You proud to call yourself a police officer?
是的
Yes.
哪怕在其他改造人面前
Even in front of other chromes?
我告訴過你  說來話長
I told you it's a long story.
你快樂嗎
Are you happy?
是的  我很快樂
Yeah, I am.
每次抓到壞人都很快樂
Every time I get a bad guy.
那我們去幫你弄那段監控視頻吧
Then let's get you that surveillance video.
頭條新聞最新進展
Updating our top story--
警方拒絕承認
police officials refuse to confirm
對"美女殺手"的調查
an investigation into the so-called beauty killer.
但是據相關人員透露
But sources close to the probe
對一個潛在連環殺手的搜捕
say the hunt for a possible serial murderer
正在緊張進行中
is underway and intensifying.
克萊爾·張為您報...
This is Claire Chang re...
魯迪
Rudy.
你們來了
You're here.
可算來了
Finally.
一小時前陵墓送來了三具復原尸體
Mausoleum dropped off three of the exhumed bodies an hour ago.
還有
And...
你說對了
you were right.
虛擬解剖證實他們七人
Vir-topsy reveals that all seven of them
在脖子下方都有一樣的傷痕
have the same wound, uh, at the base of the neck.
他們的確是被謀殺的
They were indeed murdered.
看一下
Have a look.
知道是什么造成的嗎
Any idea what caused it?
我也許知道
I might, yeah.
有什么不對勁嗎
Something wrong?
你們知道外頭有個"美女殺手"
You've got this "Beauty killer" out there,
可我卻是從新聞里得知的
and I have to hear about it on the news.
你們就沒想要警告我一下嗎
You don't think to warn me?
我跟這七名被害人有什么區別
What's the difference between me and all seven of these victims?
說啊  我來告訴你吧
Hmm? I'll tell you.
他們都死了
They're all dead.
你是在擔心自己可能成為目標嗎
You're worried that you're gonna be targeted?
我小時候當過模特
I was a child model.
長著羅思柴爾德家族的鼻子
I-I have a Rothschild's nose.
我祖母是第六位堂親繼承人
My grandmother's a sixth cousin of the heir.
是我疏忽了  魯迪
It was an oversight, Rudy.
我們很抱歉
Uh, we're sorry.
下次一定注意
Duly noted.
你有什么發現嗎
So what did you find?
傷口有線索
Something in the wound.
頭一厘米是非常干凈的貫穿口
First centimeter, a very clean insertion point,
與針刺特征吻合
consistent with a needle.
但之后就奇怪了  毫無規律
After that, it gets weird. It's irregular.
-看起來像小爪印  -就是
- Looks like tiny claw marks. - They are.
納米機器人造成的
From nanobots.
納米機器人
Nanobots?
你是說機器人被注射進他們的脖子里
Are you saying robots were injected into their necks,
在他們腦子里一通亂搗  導致了死亡嗎
crawled inside their skulls and killed them?
對  跟布萊恩·巴羅一樣
Yeah, same as Brian Barrow.
其實  他們發現其中兩個還殘存在他體內
In fact, they found two of these things still inside him.
我管它們叫麥克與艾克
I call them Mike and Ike.
你知道麥克與艾克是用來做什么的嗎
Any idea what Mike and Ike are designed to do?
我正在努力
I'm working on it.
在伊萊克特斯俱樂部干得漂亮
Great work at the Electus Club.
我很驚訝他們沒有反抗就交出了帶子
I'm amazed they gave up the tape without a fight.
謝謝
Thanks.
你在想什么
What's on your mind?
我在想也許跟改造人打交道
I'm thinking maybe it wasn't so bad
也沒有那么糟糕
being around chromes after all.
上次你跟改造人打交道
The last time you dealt with chromes,
你在射擊場待了三個小時
you were at the shooting range for three hours.
可憐的靶子都不知道自己被什么打了
Poor targets didn't know what hit them.
是啊
Yeah, well...
也許有時候人是會變的
I guess we can all be surprised.
我太過執著于不滿自己的出生
I spent so much time resenting where I came from
卻忘了他們也是人
that I forgot they're people, too.
其實  跟一些相似的人
You know, sometimes it's nice to connect with people
懂自己的人聊天  感覺挺好
who are like you who understand you.
所以你把肯尼思留在身邊
Is that why you keep Kennex around?
不
No.
因為我打賭輸了
I lost a bet.
隊長
Captain.
面部識別取得搜索結果
看來面部識別找到匹配對象了
Looks like facial rec has a match.
斯塔
Stahl.
我拿到了伊萊克特斯俱樂部的監控錄像
Hey. I got the footage from the Electus Club.
我發給你
I'm sending you a file.
有什么發現
What do you got?
布萊恩·巴羅五點半離開了俱樂部
I have Brian Barrow leaving the club at 5:30.
繼續看..
Keep watching...
-這里  -穿著外套的家伙
- There!  - The guy in the coat?
對  我覺得這就是我們要找的人
Yup. I think that's our guy.
他跟蹤巴羅到了雷明頓
He follows Barrow down Remington.
在第六大道附近
Comes around Sixth Avenue.
我從街對面的比特幣交易所
And then I get a facial recognition
拿到了面部識別的畫面
from the Bitcoin exchange across the street.
結果顯示此人名叫亞力克·戈文
Comes up as Alec Govain.
這是其中一名死者
That's one of the dead victims.
對
Correct.
還沒完
It's not over.
他在下個街角出現了
He comes around the next corner.
出租車停車場的攝像頭拍到他了
Now a camera from the cab stand picks him up.
這次的面部識別顯示他是托德· 帕克斯頓
This time, facial rec reads him as Todd Paxton.
另一名死者
Another victim.
一個人怎么會有兩種不同的面部識別結果
How could one man come up on facial rec as two different people?
我好像明白了
I think I have an answer.
-給你  -謝謝
- There you are. - Thank you.
需...  需要什么嗎
Can... can I help you?
一大杯尼多樂
One large Nitro.
馬上就好
Coming right up.
這些納米機器人內部的程序功能在于
What these nanobots are programmed to do,
讀取信息之后重建面部組織
they read and reconstruct facial tissue.
他在說什么
What did he say?
他說這位殺手會竊取受害人面部的一部分
He said our killer is stealing parts of people's faces.
有人說過你的眼睛很漂亮嗎
Did anyone ever tell you you have very pretty eyes?
這叫作納米機器人整形手術
This is about nanobot plastic surgery.
完美的你
我們找倫道夫·阿米爾博士
Dr. Randolph Amir.
不好意思
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
等等  你們不能進入...
Stop! You're not allowed to be in...
倫道夫·阿米爾博士
Dr. Randolph Amir?
是
Yes.
我們知道你參與了納米機器人
We understand that you're involved in the research
面部重建的研究
into nanobot facial reconstruction.
我等下打給你
Yeah, I'm gonna call you back.
這個想法是項新技術
The idea was a new technology.
納米機器人去皺術已經達到原子層面的水平了
Nanobot facelifts on an atomic level.
不會再有激光損傷
No more laser nips and tucks.
微小機器人按照設定程序
Microscopic robots programmed
從內部重建面部構造
to rebuild the face from the inside.
沒有疤痕  至少外面看沒有
Not a single scar. At least not on the outside.
-然后  -后來...
- And?  - And...
進展得不是很順利
it did not go well.
我沒有參與實驗
I wasn't involved in the trials.
不過我得承認我是
But I have to admit I was
第一批真正對它有信心的人
one of the first people to really believe in it.
我們至今仍弄不明白
We still don't know why.
不明白什么
Why what?
它為什么會使人心臟驟停
It was stopping people's hearts.
在受害者身上  我們找到了一個傷口
On the victim, we found a mark right at the...
就在頭骨底部
At the base of the skull.
用來從頸部植入納米機器人的儀器
Yeah, the device that inserts the nanobots into the neck
叫做實現器
is called an actuator.
打個比方
Uh, let's say
你想擁有他的完美鼻梁
you wanted his perfect nose.
實現器會將納米機器人
The actuator injects the nanobots
注射進指定區域
into the target area.
它們的作用是收集他的遺傳藍圖
They're programmed to collect his genetic blueprint.
然后通過實現器提取出來
Then the actuator would draw them out again,
再注射進你的體內
and then they'd be injected into you.
即客戶體內
The patient.
將你的鼻梁重塑成他的樣子
Rebuilding your nose to look exactly like his.
這一切都在人體內進行
All done from the inside.
唯一的問題是
The problem was
由納米機器人引發的電流
the electricity caused by the nanobots
不知為何會導致基因捐獻者心律不齊
somehow triggered an arrhythmia in the donor's heart
甚至完全停止跳動
until it stopped.
基因捐獻者會因此死亡
The donors were dying.
研究中一些接受改造者
Some of the recipients in the study
也發生了嚴重的毀容
were substantially disfigured.
在哪里可以獲得實現器
Where would someone find an actuator
用來進行這項手術
to do this procedure?
納米機器人完美地復制了他們的遺傳藍圖
The nanobots followed their blueprint perfectly.
你馬上就能獲得夢寐以求的面孔了
You're one step closer to your ideal face.
我們繼續吧
Let's keep going.
就是現在
Now.
你何時才會滿足呢  艾瑞克
When will it ever be enough, Eric?
你知道我很清楚這事的風險
You know I know all about the risks.
你也知道我根本不在乎
You know I don't care.
你對我做過的事比死亡還可怕
What you did to me was worse than dying.
你可是自愿參加試驗的
You volunteered for the trials.
動手吧
Do it.
我不喜歡那東西帶給我的感覺
I don't like what that stuff does to me.
你很清楚我需要讓你體內充滿腎上腺素
You know I have to flood your system with adrenaline,
以增強你的體能
boost your physical strength,
否則你絕對扛不住
or you will never survive
在這么短時間內進行兩次手術
another procedure so soon.
它們真漂亮
They're beautiful.
知道嗎  有缺陷是正常的  約翰
You know, it's okay to have flaws, John.
你說什么就是什么吧
Whatever helps you sleep.
據說  缺陷越多
It is said that the more flaws you have,
才說明你越像人類
the more human you are.
我最近有夸過你很有人味嗎
Have I told you how very human you are lately?
知道嗎  有時候你的嘴巴動啊動啊
You know, sometimes when you're doing this,
但我根本沒在聽
I'm not really listening.
我的缺陷還真不好找
I don't have that many flaws.
你的左眼比右眼
Your left eye is one half millimeter
高了1.5毫米
higher than the right.
你的鼻子比正常水平寬了將近一英寸了
Your nose has an abnormality one inch from the base.
那是因為我臉上挨過一拳
Yeah, that's from being punched in the face.
這樣更有性格
Adds character.
你那兩條濃密的眉毛都連在一起了
You have a fertile unibrow
收拾它們得花不少時間吧
that you tend to regularly.
至少這是我自己的臉
At least it's my face.
是我與生俱來的
I know where I came from.
你是人工合成的  誰知道你是從哪來的
You're a composite; who knows where you came from?
好好想想吧
Just think about that.
我是肯尼思
Kennex.
約翰  你在哪
Hey, John, where are you?
我正在去唐人街的路上
I'm on my way to Chinatown.
在隔離墻附近
Near the Wall.
我們發現了另一名受害者
We've got another victim.
你有什么發現
What have you got?
我有一個線人
I have an informant who knows everything
對黑市了如指掌
about the black market.
我們正在試圖尋找實現器
We're trying to find an actuator.
實現器是什么
What's an actuator?
就是兇手用來殺害這些人的東西
It's what our guy is using to kill these people.
我試試能不能找到一個購買者
I want to see if I can track one,
看看他是從哪兒弄到的
find out where he got it.
最新的受害者也死于相同作案手法
The latest victim has the same M.O.
心跳停止
Heart stops,
頸后有細小傷口
small wound at the back of the neck.
約翰  之前的七次謀殺是每月一次
John, the last seven murders were each a month apart,
而最近兩次是在48小時內
and the last two victims were within 48 hours.
這個人加快了速度
This guy's accelerating.
我們得阻止他
We need to stop him.
你咀嚼東西的時候張著嘴
You chew with your mouth open,
你不承認在頭發上用了發膠
you lie about putting gel in your hair,
你睡覺還打鼾
and you snore.
你怎么知道我睡覺打鼾
How do you know I snore?
你的智能床告訴我的
Your smartbed told me.
沒想到你跟我的床這么有感情
Oh, I didn't realize you two had a relationship.
它還告訴你什么了
What else did it tell you?
我不知道
I don't know.
我已經從我的數據庫中刪除了
Whatever it was, I purged it from my data.
顯然不是我想要記住的東西
Apparently, I didn't want to remember.
很好
Good.
這個線人長什么樣
So what does this informant look like?
如果見到他我會認出來的
I'll know him when I see him.
我討厭見到機器人被用于這種娛樂
I hate to see robots used for entertainment like this.
你認識一個叫迪卡羅的人嗎
You know a guy called Dicarlo?
不認識
No.
你在干什么  老兄
What are you doing, man?
你好  迪卡羅
Hey, Dicarlo.
該死  肯尼思
Damn it, Kennex!
我還以為你死了
I thought you were dead.
見到我高興嗎
Glad to see me?
你知不知道這些東西有多貴
Do you have any idea how expensive these things are?
多里安  這是迪卡羅
Dorian, Dicarlo.
迪卡羅  這是多里安
Dicarlo, Dorian.
那是我最喜歡的偽裝外套
That was my favorite exosuit.
里面超級舒服
Super comfy on the inside
外表又超級甜美
and sweet like pie on the outside.
我需要你幫我個忙
Look, I need your help.
我要找一個叫實現器的東西
I want to find something called an actuator.
外表是這樣
That's what it looks like.
看圖
Look at it.
-我在看呢  -認真看
- I am looking. - Look at it like you mean it.
它被用于非法的高端整容手術
It's used in illegal high-end plastic surgery.
整容手術
Plastic surgery?
就是你想要誰的臉  就得把他殺了
Yeah, the kind that kills the person whose face you want.
你知道在哪兒能找到這種東西嗎
You know where I can find something like that?
幫你我有什么好處
What do I get out of it?
你要么出于善心幫助我們
Look, you either help us out of the goodness of your heart,
要么我就讓我的機器人把你
or I'll get my robot to toss you
和你的套裝扔墻上
and your suit over the Wall.
好吧  聽著
Okay, look,
有這么一個人  只要把你的臉加熱
there's a guy, and if there's heat on you,
他就能改變你的臉
he can change your face
讓面部識別系統無法認出你來
so facial rec won't recognize you.
這人是醫生嗎
Is this guy a doctor?
我不知道  也許吧
I don't know. Probably.
在哪兒能找到他
Where do we find him?
就在東站
In the East Term.
警察  開門
Police. Open up.
-警察  開門  -不  不
- Police. Open up.  - No, no, no.
需要幫忙嗎
A little help here?!
他心跳驟停了
He's gone into cardiac arrest.
他死了
He's dead.
好像注射了合成腎上腺素
Looks like he took a shot of synthetic adrenaline.
他力量大得嚇人
He was freakishly strong.
我以為他要拼命闖出去
Thought he was gonna fight his way out.
不管他干過什么  反正他死也不愿被抓
Whatever this guy was into, he didn't want to get caught.
可不是嘛
You think?
他是柯蒂斯·麥肯醫生
His name is Dr. Curtis McCann.
那是生前了
Was.
他是參與納米機器人試驗的二十個醫生之一
He was one of the 20 doctors involved in the nanobot trials.
因為隱匿副作用
He lost his medical license
而丟掉了行醫執照
for hiding the side effects.
多里安  這就是我們要找的人
Dorian, here's the guy we're looking for.
這張臉是幾個被害人的
This face is a composite
相貌特征復合而成的
of the specific features of the victims.
面部構造包括十個部分
There are ten parts to this facial construction.
都來自他想要的特征
These are the facial features he wants.
而目前只有九位被害人
There have only been nine victims so far.
意味著他還有一個目標
Means there's still one out there.
你能推測出下一位受害人是誰嗎
Can you extrapolate who the next victim's gonna be?
根據面部識別記錄  應該是他
According to facial rec, this looks like the next victim.
兇手好像在找合適的顴骨結構
Looks like he selected the cheekbone structure.
斯塔  我覺得
Stahl, we think we know
我們找到兇手的下一個目標了
who the next victim's going to be.
別動  警察
Freeze! This is the police.
全面搜查房間
Sweep the perimeter.
喬納森·格迪斯
Jonathan Geddes?
什么情況
What the hell is this?
我們是來保護你的
We're here to protect you.
有什么收獲嗎
What have you got?
還沒有
Nothing yet.
我們在樓下安排了便衣警察
We've got a plainclothes downstairs,
就算他能繞過便衣上樓
but we're ready for him up here
樓上也有人等著他
if he makes it past him.
還有兇手身份的其他信息嗎
Any more info on the killer's I.D.?
已經傳喚保險公司
We subpoenaed the insurance company to get the names
調取試驗對象的名單
of the patients in the trials.
搞定那些繁文冗節估計要花上幾天時間
Might take a few days to get through the red tape.
但我們來不及了
We don't have that long.
我知道
Tell me about it.
等一下
Hold on a minute.
來電
誰打來的
Who is it?
-號碼被干擾了  -接起來
- The call is scrambled. - Answer it.
-我說什么  -不知道
- And say what? - I don't know.
模仿他的聲音
Just-just use his voice, you know,
就像以前你模仿我的一樣
like you... like you do mine.
我從沒聽過他的聲音
I have never heard his voice.
我只聽過他揍你時發出的低吼聲
I've only heard him grunt when he was kicking your ass.
這下好了
Terrific.
喂  我在聽了  抱歉
Hey, I'm back. Sorry.
只剩下最后一塊拼圖  他不會就此罷休的
He's not gonna give up when he's just one piece away.
他選擇受害人非常細心
He's been selecting his victims carefully.
他總會找到其他人  有他想要的面部特征
He'll find someone else with the feature he needs.
這是早晚的事
It's just a matter of time.
他是怎么選擇受害人的
How was he choosing his victims?
他心里有個完美的構想
He has the perfect face in mind,
然后去找擁有這些特征的受害者
and he's found the victims with those features.
還有一個共同點
They have one other thing in common.
他們都住在下城區
They all live in the Lower Term.
這下能把范圍縮小到50萬人口了
Well, that narrows it down to half a million... people.
怎么了
What is it?
你們看我的駕照  發現了什么沒
Take a look at my driver's license. What do you see?
駕駛許可證
一張丑陋的證件照  你應該重拍一次
A terrible picture. You should have it redone.
對  我試了  不過得排隊等好幾小時
Yeah, I tried, but you have to wait in line for hours
才能拿到新的3D照片  就是這些人用的那種
to get the new 3-D pictures, which all of these people have.
也許他們的居住地址就是模式所在
Maybe where they lived is the pattern after all.
交叉對比一下車管所的轄區
Overlay the DMV district.
他們都屬于同一轄區
They all fall in the same district.
你認為那個家伙在車管所工作嗎
Do you think the guy works at the DMV?
這是我們唯一的線索了
That's the only connection we have.
我們去查查看吧
Let's check it out.
嗨  在嗎
你好呀
亞利桑那州天氣怎么樣
又曬又熱
我很期待你下周來城里
我也是
真不敢相信我們終于要見面了
有點緊張:)
警方宣稱納米機器人手術謀殺案件獲得了進展
對不起我得走了  回聊
好的  么么噠
伙計們
Guys.
我有發現了
I got something.
什么情況
What'd you find?
我想我找到他了
I think I found him.
他確實在車管所工作
He did work at the DMV.
駕駛許可證
他叫艾瑞克·萊瑟姆
His name is Eric Latham.
能確定就是他嗎
Can we be sure it's him?
他受傷致殘的時間
He went on disability
是一年前的9月9日
September 9, a year ago.
正是測試開始的時間
That's when the trials were beginning.
你認為他還能獲取車管所文件嗎
Do you think he still has access to the DMV files?
可以  嚴格說來  他還是職員
He could. Technically, he's still an employee.
過去七年中他接受了32次手術
He's had 32 surgeries in the last seven years.
他為什么要志愿參加這些測驗呢
Why would he volunteer for these trials?
看起來完全正常
He looks perfectly normal.
在他的醫療記錄里
And there's nothing in his medical history
也沒有說他被毀過容
that shows he was disfigured, either.
也可能是得了畸形恐懼癥
Could be dysmorphic disorder.
他看周圍都是完美的形象
He sees images of perfection all around him,
他越把自己和那些形象相比
and the more he compares himself to those images,
對自己感覺就越糟
the worse he feels about himself,
然后他就被迫采取行動
and he's compelled to take the steps
來改善他在鏡子中
to mitigate the disaster
所看到的丑陋形象
he sees in the mirror.
長得丑不算什么災難
That's not a disaster.
對他來說就是
To him, it is.
他希望成為自己眼中的完美形象
He wants to be his version of perfect.
去抓住他
Go get him.
做得好
Good job.
臥室沒人
Bedroom's clear!
浴室沒人
Bathroom's clear.
沒人
Clear!
他跑了
He's gone.
四號代碼  本區域安全
Code four-- area is secure.
他的電腦終端加了密
His terminal's encrypted.
你找到什么了
What do you got?
他用了一張合成的
He's using a composite picture
理想面孔作為他的替身
of his ideal face as his avatar.
唯一的交流對象是一個女人
His only correspondence was with one woman.
現在在線  他們每天都聊天
Online. They chatted every day.
她是誰
Who is she?
她的網名叫朱蒂
Her screen name is Judy.
他們今早聯系過
They communicated this morning.
他們通信有幾個月了
They've been corresponding for months.
他聲稱自己住在亞利桑那州
He told her he lives in Arizona.
但從沒見過面
They've never met,
不過他用的是真名
but he's using his real name.
我想她不是受害人
I don't think she's a victim.
他是為了她才開始完善自己的臉
He's perfecting his face for her.
有她的地址嗎
Have you got her address?
只有網名
All I have is a screen name.
再給我點時間  就能通過她的
With a little time, I think I can track her
網絡地址追蹤到她
through her IP address.
她的頭發是深褐色的嗎
She a brunette?
是啊
Yes.
沒錯
Yes, she is.
我想我找到她了
I think I found her.
餐盒在第三個包里
The food cartridges are in the third bag.
要我幫忙嗎  朱蒂
Do you need any help, Judy?
不了  謝謝你菲爾
No, I'm fine. Thank you, Phil.
好吧
Okay.
下次見
See you next time.
朱蒂
Judy...
朱蒂  我是艾瑞克
Judy, it's Eric.
艾瑞克
Eric?
我不是故意嚇你的
I didn't mean to scare you.
你的  你的門沒關
Your, uh... your door was open.
我想給你個驚喜
I meant it as a surprise.
我是說  提前來看你
Coming early, I mean.
你真美
You're beautiful.
這繃帶真不雅觀
I'm sorry about the bandage.
實際上
Truth is,
我不想讓你看見我這個樣子
I didn't want you to see me like this.
但我向你保證
But I can assure you
我很快就能拿掉這玩意兒了
I won't be wearing it for long.
我想你一定很帥
I'm sure you're beautiful.
就像我們一起聊天時
As beautiful as the feelings
那種感覺一樣美好
and the conversations we've shared.
但我有事瞞著你
But I've kept something from you.
什么事
What?
你是個盲人
You're blind.
我應該告訴你的
I should have told you.
每每想到這里我都很掙扎
I-I struggled with it every time,
可我就是
but I just...
我就是這么的喜歡你
I-I just liked you so much,
而且你也喜歡我
and-and you liked me,
我不希望這段關系就此結束
and I didn't want it to end,
我真的很怕
and I was afraid it would.
如果你能愛上我
If you could love me...
就會知道我和你一開始認識并關心的人
then you would see that I am the same person
沒有任何區別
that you began to know and care about.
我就是覺得
I just felt
你和我
that you were...
一樣孤獨
as lonely as I was.
我沒說錯吧
Was I wrong?
沒錯
No.
我不在乎你的長相
I don't care about your face,
也不在乎你現在是什么樣子  我就是
or-or what you look like. I just...
我實在太高興了  我們找到了彼此
I'm so happy that we found each other.
你哭了
You're crying.
-艾瑞克  艾瑞克  -警察  不許動
- Eric! Eric! - Police! Police! Freeze!
警察  伍德女士  呆在原地
Police! Ms. Wood, stay where you are.
嫌疑人在樓里
Suspect on premises.
到此為止  艾瑞克
It's over, Eric.
下來  艾瑞克
Come down from there, Eric.
我明白你的感受
Look, I understand how you must be feeling.
沒必要走到這個地步
It doesn't have to end like this.
你叫什么
What's your name?
我叫約翰
It's John.
你可曾被人愛過  約翰
Have you ever been loved, John?
有的
I have.
那你是不會明白的
Then you wouldn't understand.
我們都有被愛的權利
We're supposed to be loved.
你沒事吧
You okay?
沒事  我很好
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
你認為在這座城市里的人
Do you think, with all the people in this city--
甚至說整個世界
in the world--
總有一個人是屬于你的嗎
that there's someone out there for everyone?
我想是的
I do.
思想真夠老派的
That's old-fashioned.
我就是這樣的
That's me.
思想老派
Old-fashioned.
就算是我的機器人也有停用的時候
Even my robot's discontinued.
你要我和你一塊去酒吧
Do you want me to come to a bar with you
看你喝酒嗎
and watch you drink?
不
No.
不用了
No, that's okay.
上次那樣有點奇怪
That, uh... got a little weird last time.
晚安  約翰
Good night, John.
約翰
Hey, John.
嗨
Hey.
你要回家嗎
You going home?
是的  剛剛還在考慮呢
Yeah, I was thinking about it.
我可能會去喝一杯
I might head out for a drink.
你聽說過一個叫獅子宮的酒吧嗎
You ever heard of a place called Leo's?
我現在正準備要去呢
That's actually where I'm going right now.
我很喜歡那間酒吧
I love that place.
你開玩笑吧  說真的嗎
Come on. You're kidding me. Really?
-真的  -斯塔警探
- Yeah. - Detective Stahl.
你好
Hi.
抱歉  我沒打斷你們吧
I'm sorry. I'm... not interrupting, am I?
沒有  完全沒有
No. No, not at all.
杰克  這是約翰
Jake, this is John.
你好
Hey. How are you?
-收拾好了嗎  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
一會酒吧見咯
Will I see you there?
好  我一會自己晃過去吧
Yeah. Yeah, I might swing along.
不過...
You know, but...
我還有幾份報告要寫呢
got a few reports to finish, but...
你倆玩得開心點
You guys have fun.
工作別太辛苦哦
Don't work too hard.
*Worlds away*
*With memories*
*Of killing time and dreams*
*Think of me*
*It was so cold*
*We burned*
*And as they leave*
*They cross my mind*
*No time*
*I think it's over*
*This life inside I seem to mind ?*
*Look in your eyes, you're worlds away... ?*